

PROFILE

I am a professional who seeks to grow in his career by finding better ways to do my job and to make it easier by finding solutions that help others.

I like to optimize and work hard in order to meet the objectives and goals that are proposed or imposed on me.

Continuing to learn and train myself is something I do a lot, which has served me in the jobs I've had and I'm sure it will continue to serve me.

INFORMATION

DNI: 0956332050

BIRTHDAY: 11/Dec/1995

ADDRESS: Durán - Los Helechos - Mz. R

– Sector 6 – Solar 20

PHONES: <u>0982686560</u> – <u>0987445927</u>

EMAIL:

edgarguitarist@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO WEB:

https://edgarguitarist.github.io

REPOSITORIES:

https://github.com/edgarguitarist

SKILLS

Languages:

Intermediate English - B1 (Cambridge).

Teamwork.

Ease of Communication.

Proactivity.

Adaptability.

Organized.

Polyvalent.

Without fear of success!

EDGAR MARIANO LAZ TERÁN

COMPUTER AND INFORMATICS ENGINEER

EDUCATION

Private school – Liceo Cristiano de Durán

2012 - 2014

President of the Student Council of the College.

Universidad Agraria del Ecuador

2014 - 2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

ELCAP S.A - Supervisor

2015 - 2015

Control of Employees, Sales and Customer Service in the Call Center.

Hotel Oro Verde – Waitress

2015 - 2018

Customer Service and Organization of Events.

911PC – Network Technician

2018 - 2018

Design and Implementation of Networks for Companies, Hotels and others.

Purchase and Sale of Resources for Camera Networks and Systems.

Freelance – Web and Mobile Full-Stack Developer

2019 - January 2022

Creation of Web Systems with PHP, HTML, CSS, MySQL, MariaDB, JavaScript and Native Android Applications with Java and Kotlin.

KNOWLEDGES

Programming Languages

✓ HTML
✓ JavaScript
✓ PHP

✓ CSS

✓ TypeScript

✓ Java/Kotlin

Database Management Systems

✓ MySQL ✓ PostgreSQL ✓ MongoDB ✓ Firebase

Libraries & Frameworks

✓ Node.js
✓ Express.js
✓ Tailwind

✓ React.js
✓ Next.js

